chitongs.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy

###  **1\. General**

Chitongs.com puts users privacy at the first place and makes a commitment to protect their personal information. This policy gives an explanation of how personal information is treated. Before you made a decision to use our website, please spare a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy carefully. Once you visit our website or accept the service we provide, it means you have totally consented to the Privacy Policy below and the updated version.

###  **2\. Collection & Use of Your Information**

chitongs.com is sole owner of the information collected on this website. The information we obtained from you is used to build the database which will help us review, develop, and improve our services.

(1)What kind of information do we collect?

We collect all the information in your account on chitongs.com, such as your name, address, company name, telephone number, fax number and email address, etc. In addition to your account data, we also collect records information when you browse and visit our website, including but not limited to cookies, IP address, etc.

(2)How do we use the information we collect?

We collect all the information in your account on chitongs.com, such as your name, address, company name, telephone number, fax number and email address, etc. In addition to your account data, we also collect records information when you browse and visit our website, including but not limited to cookies, IP address, etc.

###  **3\. Security Measures**

We have taken appropriate measures to safeguard the privacy of your personal information. And we have implemented relevant technology to encrypt your account avoiding being divulged or viciously modified. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. However, no method of transmission on the internet can guarantee 100% security, but we will strive to make your private information much safer.

###  **4\. To whom we Disclose Your Personal Information?**

We will not disclose your information unless we have ample reasons to believe that such disclosure is necessary in the following cases:

(1) Within your authorization;

(2) You are willing to share your information publicly;

(3) Required by law, legal procedures, or government enforcement;

(4) Aiming at academic research or public service;

(5) In order to safeguard rights of chitongs.com, such as searching, preventing, and handling fraud or security issues.

###  **5\. Modifications**

chitongs.com will at its sole discretion identify and correct the inaccuracies which may occur in our terms. If any modification is made, we will make you aware of what information we collect, how to use it and under what circumstances. It depends on your own choice whether we are authorized to use your information we collected. No authorization is sure to affect our capabilities in providing you with our best service.

###  **6\. Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information that a website can store in a designated file on your computer. When you browse a website, cookies could help you improve your web surfing experience. We use cookies to gather and record your surfing information, with which we can provide you with tailored information to your needs. And also cookies can save your time when you re-enter your account. Many browsers are designed to accept cookies, but you can set your browsers to refuse cookies. One point should be noted that if you elect to disable our cookies, you will not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience on our website.

###  **7\. Disclaimers**

For the convenience of your surfing experience, we may post links of other web sites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites not operated by us. Before you visit relevant websites, please read relating privacy statements of each. This privacy statement applies solely to the information collected by chitongs.com.

###  **8\. Contact us**

If you should have any complains or concerns pertaining to this privacy policy, please contact us by visiting chitongs.com.
